Guide to the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 Records WAG.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX: Addendum, General Files.
  - Legal: Manos and Carvelas vs. Local 6, et al., 1978 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Legislation (Assembly Bill #6013), 1976 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Lexington Hotel, 1977;1979; 1997 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Lexington Hotel: Strike Threat, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Local 1, Dining Room Employees, undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Local 2 (San Francisco), Aug 1980- Jan 1981 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Local 6 Liberator, 1951 (Box Shared Tamiment 007, Folder 3)
  - Local 17 (Los Angeles), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Local 30 (San Diego): Transfer to Local 6, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Local 56 (I.B.F.O): Transfers, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Local 69: Merger, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Local 69: New Jersey Shops Per Capita Reports [Restricted], 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Local 69: Steven Wilson, Jan 1981- Mar 1981 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Local 89, Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks, and Assistants, undated;1950 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Local 100: Collective Bargaining Educational Coursebook (M.E.M.O.), 1996 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Local 144 Defense Fund, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Local 144: Transfers, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Local 153: Executive Board Resolutions, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Local 424 (United Industry Workers), 1986-1988 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Local 481: organizing ("Join a Real Union"), [1978] (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Local Joint Organizing Committee, 1974;1976 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Loews Corp: Hiring Practices, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Loews Howard Johnson Plaza Hotel: Café 52, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Long John Silver, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Lotos Club, 1978-1980 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Lotos Club: Bargaining, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Lowell, Hotel: Agreement Between Local 6 and Alan Stillman, Apr 10, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Macklowe Hotel: Picket Line, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Madison Towers, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Manhattan Courtyard: Bargaining, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Manhattan Plaza: Performing Arts Residential Community, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Maritime Port Council of Greater New York, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Marley, James, 1967-1973 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Marriot East Hotel, 1993-1994 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Marriot Marquis Hotel: Picket Expenses, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Marriot Marquis Hotel: Picket Line, [1995] (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Mayfair Regent Hotel, 1979-1985 (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - Mayflower Coffee Shop: Grievances, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Mayflower Hotel, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - McAlpin House, 1976-1978; 1984- 1985 (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - McAlpin House: Grievances, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Membership Books, 1970-1971; 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - Membership Meeting Flyers, 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Membership Roster [Restricted], 1987 (Box 59, Folder 52)
  - Membership Survey [Restricted], 1994 (Box 59, Folder 53)
  - Menus, undated (Box 59, Folder 54)
  - Merchants Club, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 55)
  - Metropole Hotel, 1982-1984 (Box 59, Folder 56)
  - Metropolitan Club, 1976-1978; 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 57)
  - Metropolitan Club: Agreements, 1978;1981; 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 58)
  - Metropolitan Club: Arbitrations, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 59)
  - Metropolitan Club; Grievances, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 60)
  - Metropolitan Opera Club, 1981;1984 (Box 59, Folder 61)
  - Metropolitan Opera Club: Agreement, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 62)
  - Mets Motel, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 63)
  - Michelangelo Hotel: Bargaining, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 64)
  - Midtown Suites Hotel: Organizing, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 65)
  - Midway Motor Inn, 1979;1984 (Box 59, Folder 66)
  - Milburn Hotel, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 67)
  - Milford Plaza Hotel, 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 68)
  - Millennium Broadway, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 69)
  - Millennium Broadway: Organizing, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Minimum Wage and Tip Allowances, 1966; 1975- 1977 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Minorities/ Minorias, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Assembly Board, 1985-1987 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Assembly Board, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Assembly Board, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Assembly Board, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Assembly Board, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees/ Advisory Committee of the Hotel Assoc. Insurance Fund, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Club Employees Pension Fund, 1977;1978 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1964-1965 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1983-1985 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1986-1988 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly Installation, Sep 28, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1964-1965 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Minutes: Executive Board (and Attendance Sheets, 1974-1977), 1975;1976 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Minutes: Executive Board (and Attendance Sheets), 1991-1992 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Executive-Investment, 1975;1977 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Insurance Fund, 1966-1976 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Insurance Fund, 1977-1978; Nov 29, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Local Joint Executive Board, 1974-1977 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Local Staff Meetings, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Meeting Schedule of Executive, Assembly, and Department Boards, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Pension Fund (Club), 1970-1979 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Special Open Assembly Meeting (Honest Ballot Association), Aug 17, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Mohawk Casino: Bargaining, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Montauk Club and Hotel: Agreements, 1962-1966; 1972-1978; 1983; 1992 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1964 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1965 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1966 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Jan 1967- Jun 1967 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Jul 1967- Dec 1967 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Jan 1970- Jun 1970 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Jul 1970- Dec 1970 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Jan 1975- Jun 1975 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Jul 1975- Dec 1975 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Jan 1976- Jun 1976 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Jul 1976- Dec 1976 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1977 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1980 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1983 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1984 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), 1986 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Monthly Financial Reports (To HERE), Dec 1989- Dec 1991 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Movenpick Restaurant, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Murray Hill Hotel, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Myrtle Beach Hotel: Organizing, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1974-1977 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1984-1985; 1998 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - National Labor Relations Board Cases, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - National Livery Service, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Navarro Hotel, 1977-1979; 1983 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Newton Hotel, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - New Years Eve City-Wide Wage Rates, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - New York Athletic Club, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - New York Athletic Club: Agreements, 1984-1986 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - New York Athletic Club: Bargaining, 1985;1986 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1976;1978 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - New York City Central Labor Council: Dislocated Workers, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - New York Commission on Human Rights, Complaint vs. HERE, Local 6, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - New York City Community College Advisory Commission, 1978-1980 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - New York City Department of Labor: Re-establishment, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Agreements, 1978;1985; 1989;1990 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Agreements (re: CIO Affiliation), 1948;1950 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Benefit Trust Funds, Nov 1986- Dec 1986 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: By-Laws, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: COPE, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Industry Training Program, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Insurance Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Insurance Fund Health Center Informational Brochure and Questionnaire, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Pension Fund Trustees' Meetings, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Remittances, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Theatrical Production, "The Call", [1993] (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - New York City Hotel Trades Council: Wage Policy Committee, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - New York Hotel Trades Council: Wage Policy Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - New Yorker Hotel, 1953;1979 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - New York Palace: Bargaining, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - New York State Labor Relations Board, 1967;1977 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - New York Vista: Explosion, Feb 1993 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Novotel, 1984;1994 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Publications, [1947] (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Obermeier, Michael: Deportation Proceedings, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Olcott Hotel: Grievances, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - OPEIU, Local 153: Agreement with Local 6, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Opposition Membership Party, 1966;1975 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Organizer's Weekly Reports (Vito Pitta), 1991-1992 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Organizing Sourcebook, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - "Organizing Techniques" Seminar, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Overseas Press Club, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Paramount and Royalton, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - Park Central Hotel: Arbitrations, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Parklane Hotel, 1974;1977-1979 (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Paul Revere Chop House: Retroactive Wage Increase, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Pay Equalization, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Penn Club: Bargaining, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Pennsylvania, Hotel: Grievances, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Pennsylvania, Hotel: Penn bar Closure Grievances, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Pension Fund, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Pension Fund, 1976;1983 (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Pension Fund: Club Department, 1957;1977 (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - Pension Fund: Club Department, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - Pension Fund: Declaration of Trust (NYHTC and Hotel Assoc.), 1952 (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Pension Fund: Martin E. Segal Co., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Pension Fund: Legal Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Pension Fund: Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Pension Fund: Subcommittee on Investigations Subpoena, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Pension Fund: Summary Plan, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Pension Trust Fund, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Pension Trust Fund, 1978;1979 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Petitions, 1974-1976; 1979 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Piccadilly Hotel, 1977;1979 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Pierre Hotel, 1976-1978 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Pierre Hotel: Grievances, 1998;1999 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Pinnacle Club, 1974;1977; 1978 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Pitta, Vito: Appointment to NYS Board of Tourism, 1977;1992 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Players Club, 1979;1989-1996 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Plaza Hotel: Grievances, 1970;1974; 1978;1998 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Plaza Hotel: Thefts, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Plaza Hotel: Wages, 1975;1977 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Political Action Committee: Campaign Contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Postal Workers Strike, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Prince George Hotel, 1974;1985 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Princeton Club, undated;1976-1977;1994 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Publicity, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Puerto Rico, 1975;1978 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Puerto Rico Hurricane Relief Fund, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Quality hotel and Suites, 1998-1999 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Quality Inn, La Guardia, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Quality Inn (Riverview), 1978 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Quality Inn: Severance Forms [Restricted], 1985 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Queens Motor Inn, 1986;1999 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Racquet & Tennis Club, 1956-1996 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Raffles, 1982;1985; 1986 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Rainbow Room, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Rainbow Room, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Rainbow Room: Delegate Dispute, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Rainbow Room: "Union News" (Organizing Newsletter), 1991 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Rally: Drexel Burnham Lambert Take-Over of Holiday Inn Las Vegas, Mar 26, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Ramada Inn, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Ramada Milford: Bargaining, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Rank-and-File Committee: Anti-Rubin Flyer, [1949] (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Ratification Anniversary Day, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Real Estate Purchase on 8th Ave., Jun 14, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Recess Club, 1978-1979 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Regency Hotel: Grievances, 1970;1976 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Regency Hotel: Houseman Agreement, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Regent Hotel Neutrality Agreement, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - Report to the Union by the Local 6 Administration (1962-1965) (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - Research Institute of America, 1978-1979 (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - Restaurant Associates, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - Restaurant Division: Bargaining, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - Restaurant League of New York, Oct 1979- Jun 1981 (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - Restaurant Marketing Associates: Bargaining, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - "Retired Hotel Workers Stage Pension Protest" (NY Times), 1976 (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - Retirement Fund, 1977;1979 (Box 63, Folder 53)
  - Richman, Fredric N., 1981 (Box 63, Folder 54)
  - Richoux of London, Oct 24, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 55)
  - Ritz Towers, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 56)
  - Rive Café: Organizing, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 57)
  - River Club, 1977;1979 (Box 63, Folder 58)
  - Rockaway of New York, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 59)
  - Roger Smith Hotel, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 60)
  - Roll Call: Grievances, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 61)
  - Roosevelt Hotel, 1971;1977; 1978 (Box 63, Folder 62)
  - Royal Globe Club, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 63)
  - Royal Manhattan: Lay-Offs, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 64)
  - Russian Tearoom, Mar 1 1980- Sep 23 1981 (Box 63, Folder 65)
  - Rye Hilton, Jul 1980 (Box 63, Folder 66)
  - Sahara-Tahoe Hotel: Jerry Lewis Crosses Picket-Line, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 67)
  - St. George Hotel, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 68)
  - St. George Hotel: NY Hotel Trades Council Flyers (Organizing), 1950 (Box 63, Folder 69)
  - St. John's Hospital Strike (IAM), 1990 (Box 63, Folder 70)
  - St. Moritz Hotel: Flyers by NYHTC, AFL for Employee Election, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 71)
  - St. Moritz Hotel: Grievances, 1976;1978 (Box 63, Folder 72)
  - St. Moritz Hotel: Housekeeping Department, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 73)
  - St. Regis Hotel: Banquet Committee, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 74)
  - St. Regis Hotel: Grievances, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 75)
  - St. Regis-Sheraton, 1974;1977- 1979 (Box 63, Folder 76)
  - Salisbury Hotel: "To Help Church, He Moved to Hotel" (Bill Dukokian), Jun 17, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 77)
  - Seaman's Church Institute, Mar 1975- May 1981 (Box 63, Folder 78)
  - SEIU: Local 32b: Apartment Building Strike, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 79)
  - 760 Building Corp.: Finances, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 80)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 81)
  - Shea and Gould: Agreements, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 82)
  - Shea and Gould: Legal Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 83)
  - Sheraton Center, 1979;1984 (Box 63, Folder 84)
  - Sheraton, 44th st., 1977 (Box 63, Folder 85)
  - Sheraton Inn at La Guardia, 1978;1984 (Box 63, Folder 86)
  - Sheraton Motor-Inn, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 87)
  - Sheraton Russel, 1985-1986 (Box 63, Folder 88)
  - Sherry Netherland- L'Etoile: Grievances, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 89)
  - Shop Committee Meetings, 1974;1980; 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Silver Palace: Organizing, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Sirch, Richard; Statement to Local 6 Members (Int. Union's Supervision Over Loc. 6), 1957 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 60 East Club: Agreement, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 60 East Club: Bargaining, 1990;1995 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Sky Club, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Sky Chefs (JFK Airport. LaGuardia), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Smith's Bar and Grill, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Social Activism Support, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Social Service Department, 1976;1977; 1980 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Solidarity Cards, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - "Solidarity Forever" (Lyric Sheet), 1977 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Solidarity 2 March, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Staff: Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Staff Business Representatives, [1975] (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Staff: Appointments to Affiliates and Funds, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Staff: OPEIU, Local 153, 1966-1977 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Staff: OPEIU, Local 153, Agreements, Jun 1, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Staff: Resignations and Retirement, Feb 1980- Oct 1981 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Stanhope Hotel, 1977;1997 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Staten Island Hotel: Bargaining, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Statler Hilton Hotel, 1977;1978 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Stevens Boycott, 1977-1979 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Stipulations, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Stock Exchange Luncheon Club, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Strike: Article from United Labor Action, undated (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Subpoena Questions: National Bank of N. America, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Summit Hotel: Grievences, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Taft, Hotel, 1971;1976 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Tavern on the Green, Jun 1980-Sep 1980 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Tavern on the Green: Arbitration (Hazen Case), 1998;1999 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Tavern on the Green: Bargaining, 1989;1993 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Tavern on the Green: Grievances, 1992;1993; 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Tavern on the Green: Runners Dispute, 1995-1999 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Tavern on the Green: Unjust Termination Case, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Telegrams, Oct 1979-Jul 1981 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Ten Park Ave. Hotel, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Times Square Hotel, 1992;1999 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Tirino, Joseph/ Canning, Alvina, vs. Local 164, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - "To Ensure Progress" (T.I.P.) Fund, Oct 7, 1980- May 28, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Traffic Club: Agreement, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Transit Workers' Strike, Mar 1980 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Travellers Hotel, 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - Trial Board, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 44)
  - Tudor Hotel, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 45)
  - Union Booklet Mockup, [1966] (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - Union Club: Bargaining, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - Union Family Medical Fund: Annual Trustees Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - Union Family Medical Fund: Correspondence, 1975;1976 (Box 64, Folder 49)
  - Union Label and Service Dept, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 50)
  - Union Officer (M. Dowd): Notes, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 51)
  - Union Mine Workers vs. Pittson Coal, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 52)
  - United Nations Plaza Hotel, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 53)
  - United nations Plaza Hotel (Park Hyatt): Function Sheets, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 54)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Relations: New York State Employment Service, Feb 21, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 55)
  - United Way, 1977-1979; 1981;1984 (Box 64, Folder 56)
  - University Club, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 57)
  - University Club; Bargaining, 1986;1995 (Box 64, Folder 58)
  - University Club: Union Shop Provisions, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 59)
  - Wage Adjustment: Three Member Commission, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 60)
  - Wage Equalization, 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 61)
  - Wage Rates, 1985-1989 (Box 64, Folder 62)
  - Waiters and Waitresses Race, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 63)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Arbitration, Oct 1945 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Banquet Department, 1978-1979; 1983-1993 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Banquet Department: Herman, Julius (Delegate, Banquet Manager) Correspondence and Clippings, 1957;1958; 1960-1962; 1988 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Banquet Waiters, 1983-1995 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Barrings, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Banquet Team ("Warm-up Time" by M. Alemany), undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Business Expenses Deduction, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Delegate Cards, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Discrimination Charges, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Grievances, 1976-1978; 1998 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Lay-Offs, 1978;1979 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Night Cleaners Dispute, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Waldorf Astoria: Union Recruitment, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Wall Street Club, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Warwick Hotel, 1975;1978 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Warwick Hotel: Ciao Europa Restaurant, 1993;1995 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Weavers Club: Bargaining, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Weissman-Heller Inc., Oct 1980-Jul 1981 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Westbury Hotel: Agreements, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Westbury Hotel: Banquet Staff, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - West 86th St. Corporation: Memorandum of Understanding, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Westway Motor Inn, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Williams Club, 1978;1991 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - William Sloane House: Contract, 1967;1983 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - WIndsor Hotel: Agreements, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Woodward Hotel: Grievances, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Yacht Club: Bargaining, 1991;1994 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Yale Club: Agreements, 1987;1990 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - YMCA of Greater New York: Maids, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - YWCA: Bargaining, 1980;1992; 1995;1998 (Box 65, Folder 30)